Black _ Pearl Jam
by Maasbach Jonatan
Intro: E _ A

E                    A                E             A
Sheets of empty canvas,___ untouched sheets of clay
E                       A            E
Her legs spread out before me,___ as her body was there
                A                 E             A
All five horizons,___ revolved around her soul (as the earth to the sun)
E                A                 E
Now the air I tasted and breathed has taken a turn
   C                                      Em
Oooh and all I  taught her was... everything
   C                                 Em
Oooh  I know she gave me all... that she wore
               D                   C                                   Em
And now my bitter hands,___ Shake beneath the clouds of what was everything
            D                   C                                      Em
All the pictures have all been washed in black,____  tattooed everything.


  E        A                       E          A
I take a walk outside,___ I'm surrounded by some kids at play
E                    A           E
I can feel their laughter,___ so how do I sing
    C                                       Em
Ooh and twisted thoughts that spin round my head (I'm spinnin')
      C                          Em
Oooh how quick the sun can drop away__________
              D                  C                                 Em
And now my bitter hands cradle broken glass,__ of what was everything
         D                      C                                     Em
All the pictures have all been washed in black,____ tattooed everything
         D                         C
All the love gone bad; turned my world to black
          D                 C                        Em     D     C      Em   D    C
Tattooed all I see,___ all that I am; all that I'll be
   Em                                            D
I know some day you'll have a beautiful life; I know you'll be a sun
    C                   Em            D
In somebody else�s sky, why, why, why
           C                    Em
can't it be, can't it be in mine.

Coda:
D  C  Em

		