           Every rose has its thorn

                 (By Poison)

             Words and Music by
B.Dall, C.C.DEVILLE, B. MICHAELS and R. ROCKETT



G
..............................
C(add9)
..............................
G
We both lie silently still in the
C(add9)
dead of the night. Although we
G
both lie close together we feel
C(add9)
miles apart inside. Was it
G                C(add9)
something I said or something I did? Did my
G                        C(add9)
words not come out right? Though I
D
tried not to hurt you, though I
C
tried. But I guess that's why they say
G
ev'ry rose has its
C(add9)
thorn, just like
G
ev'ry night has its
C(add9)
dawn. Just like
G     D
ev'ry cowboy sings his
C        G
sad, sad song

ev'ry rose has its
C
thorn.
G
..............................
C(add9)
..............................
G
..............................
C(add9)
........................... I
G
listen to our favourite song paying on the
C(add9)
radio hear the
G
D.J. say love's a game of easy come and
C(add9)
easy go. But I
G              C(add9)
wonder does he know, has he
G              C(add9)
ever felt like this? And I
D
know that you'd be right now if I
C
could've let you know somehow. I guess
G
ev'ry rose has its
C(add9)
thorn, just like
G
ev'ry night has its
C(add9)
dawn. Just like
G     D
ev'ry cowboy sings his
C        G
sad, sad song

ev'ry rose has its
C(add9)
thorn.
Em                   D
Though it's been a while now I can
C                    G
still feel so much pain.
Em                      D
Like the knife thats cuts you, the wound heals,
C
but the scar, that scar re-
G
mains
C(add9)
..............................
G
..............................
C(add9)
..............................
G
I know I could have saved our love that night if I'd
C(add9)
known what to say
G
Instead of making love we both
C(add9)
made our separate ways. Now I
G                     C(add9)
hear you've found somebody new and
G                       C
that I never meant that much to you. To
D
hear thattears me up inside and to
C
see you cuts me like a knife. I guess
G
ev'ry rose has its
C(add9)
thorn, just like
G
ev'ry night has its
C(add9)
dawn. Just like
G     D
ev'ry cowboy sings his
C(add9)  G
sad, sad song

ev'ry rose has its
C(add9)
thorn.
D             G
..............................


From: torbjorn@ifi.uio.no (Torbj�rn Richardsen)


Every rose has its thorn
(Poison)


Fingering suggestions:

G                Cadd9
||---|---|-4-|   ||---|---|-4-|
||---|---|-3-|   ||---|---|-3-|
||---|---|---|   ||---|---|---|
||---|---|---|   ||---|-1-|---|
||---|-1-|---|   ||---|---|-2-|
||---|---|-2-|   ||---|---|---|


Intro: G Cadd9

G                                 Cadd9
We both lie silently still in the dead of the night. Although we
G                               Cadd9
both lie close together we feel miles apart inside. Was it
G                   Cadd9                   G                  Cadd9
something I said or something I did? Did my words not come out right? Though I
D                               C
tried not to hurt you, though I tried. But I guess that's why they say

G                  Cadd9
ev'ry rose has its thorn, just like
G                   Cadd9
ev'ry night has its dawn. Just like
G     D                C        G
ev'ry cowboy sings his sad, sad song
                   C
ev'ry rose has its thorn

G Cadd9 G Cadd9

G                                           Cadd9
Listen to our favourite song playing on the radio hear the
G                              Cadd9
D.J. say love's a game of easy come and easy go. But I
G              Cadd9        G              Cadd9
wonder does he know, has he ever felt like this? And I
D                                 C
know that you'd be right now if I could've let you know somehow. I guess

G                  Cadd9
ev'ry rose has its thorn, just like
G                   Cadd9
ev'ry night has its dawn. Just like
G     D                C        G
ev'ry cowboy sings his sad, sad song
                   C
ev'ry rose has its thorn

Em                   D             C                  G
Though it's been a while now I can still feel so much pain.
Em                   D                          C
Like the knife thats cuts you, the wound heals, but the scar,
            G      Cadd9  G  Cadd9
that scar remains

G                                                    Cadd9
I know I could have saved our love that night if I'd known what to say
G                              Cadd9
Instead of making love we both made our separate ways. Now I
G                     Cadd9        G                       Cadd9
hear you've found somebody new and that I never meant that much to you. To
D                                   C
hear that tears me up inside and to see you cuts me like a knife. I guess

G                  Cadd9
ev'ry rose has its thorn, just like
G                   Cadd9
ev'ry night has its dawn. Just like
G     D                C        G
ev'ry cowboy sings his sad, sad song
                   C     D  G
ev'ry rose has its thorn

		