{title:She Loves You}
{subtitle:Lennon/McCartney}

{c:Intro:}
    [C]She [Am]loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah. She [D7]loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah.
    She [F]loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah, [C]yeah.

You [C]think you've lost your [Am]love when I [Em]saw her yester[G7]day.
It's [C]you she's thinking [Am]of and she [Em]told me what to [G7]say.
She says she [Am]loves you and you know that can't be bad.
Yes she [F]loves you and you [Dm]know you should be [G7]glad. Oooh.

She said you were to know that she almost lost her mind.
And now she says she knows you're not the hurting kind.
She says she loves you and you know that can't be bad.
Yes she loves you and you know you should be glad. Oooh.

    She [Am]loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah. She [D7]loves you, yeah, yeah, yeah.
    and with a [F]love like that, you [G7]know you should be [C]glad.

And now its up to you, I think it's only fair.
If I should hurt you too, apologize to her.
Because she loves you, and you know that can't be bad.
Yes she loves you and you know you should be glad. Oooh.

{c:repeat Intro}

{new_song}