
Smoke A Little Smoke
By Eric Church
Tabbed By Larry Mofle
7/14/2010


Capo 1

               A
Turn the quiet up, turn the noise down
             A
Let this ol' world just spin around
                A
I wanna feel it swing, wanna feel it sway
             E               D
And put some feel good in my soul
D                     E                    A
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke


Want a little more right, and a little less left
Little more right now, a little less what's next
Act like tomorrow's ten years away
And just kick back and let the feelin' flow
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke


Bridge:
F#m                  D
I set my sails for a new direction
                       A
But the wind got in my way
F#m                        D
I changed my course but my definition of change
               E
Just ain't the same


I'm gonna sit right here stay away from there
I'm gonna make pretend I just don't care
And I could get up. go get her back
Or maybe I'll just let her go
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke


D                                    A
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke
D
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke
A
Kick back, gives the blues a spin, break out the wine, forget again
D
Dig down deep, find my stash. light it up, take me back
A
Kick back, gives the blues a spin, break out the wine, forget again
D
Dig down deep, find my stash. light it up, memory crash
A
Oh no, I don't know, baby, it might take, all night
                E                           D
Then I'll maybe break out that old rock and roll
A                     E              A
Drink a little drink, smoke a little smoke 